Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - M-O
        - Ohio Players - Everybody up, 1979; SR-27114; Ohio Players (Box 57)
        - Ohio Players - Tenderness, 1981; SR-27115; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          Catalog # FW 37090; A-side Matrix # FW-AL-37090 P-3
        - Ohio Players - Ouch!, 1981; SR-27116; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          Catalog # NB1-33247; A-side Matrix # NB1-AL-33247
        - Ohio Players - Ohio Players greatest hits, 1974; SR-27117; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27118. Different discs.
          Catalog # WB 1005; A-side Matrix # WB-1005-A
        - Ohio Players - Ecstasy, 1973; SR-27118; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27117. Different discs.
          Catalog # WB 2021; A-side Matrix # WB-2021-A
        - Ohio Players - Sweat, 1988; SR-27119; Ohio Players (Box 57)
          Catalog # TRK-58813-1; A-side Matrix # TRK-58813-A
          Track Record Company
          Seattle, Washington
        - O'Jays - So full of love, 1978; SR-27120; O'Jays (Box 57)
          Catalog # JZ 35355; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AL-35355-1D
        - O'Jays - The year 2000, 1980; SR-27121; O'Jays (Box 57)
          Catalog # FZ 36416; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AL-36416-1A
        - Okosun, Sonny - Liberation, 1984; SR-27122; Okosun, Sonny (Box 57)
          Catalog # SHANACHIE 43019; A-side Matrix # SH-43019A
        - Okosun, Sonny - Which way Nigeria?, 1984; SR-27123; Okosun, Sonny (Box 57)
          Catalog # JL-8-8247; A-side Matrix # OL88247-SA-RCA1
          Hive Afrika
        - Olatunji - Drum shots, 1974; SR-27124; Olatunji (Box 57)
          Catalog # TLP-5014; A-side Matrix # SLT-00757
          Trip Jazz
          Linden, New Jersey
        - Olatunji and his Percussion, Brass, Woodwind, and Choir - Zungo!, 1961; SR-27125; Olatunji and his Percussion, Brass, Woodwind, and Choir (Box 57)
          Catalog # CL 1634; A-side Matrix # XLP52897-1AA
        - Olsson, Nigel - Changing tides, 1980; SR-27126; Olsson, Nigel (Box 57)
          Catalog # JZ 36491; A-side Matrix # AL-36491-1K
          Bang Records
        - Olympic Runners - Out in front, 1975; SR-27127; Olympic Runners (Box 57)
          Catalog # PS 658; A-side Matrix # SAHS 1668 PP
        - O'Malley, Lenore - Lenore, 1981; SR-27128; O'Malley, Lenore (Box 57)
          Catalog # PD-1-6321; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6321-AS-PW
        - Omni - Out of my hands (love's taken over), 1981; SR-27129; Omni; Draper, Connee (Box 57)
          Catalog # FRD-81-1; A-side Matrix # FRD-81-1
          Fountain Records
        - Omni Trio - Music for the next millennium (disc one), 1995; SR-27130; Omni Trio (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27131. Double album.
          Catalog # SM-8012; A-side Matrix # SM-8012-A (SIDE 1)
        - Omni Trio - Music for the next millennium (disc two), 1995; SR-27131; Omni Trio (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27130. Double album.
          Catalog # SM-8012; A-side Matrix # SM-8012-C (SIDE 3)
        - One Cause One Effect - Up with hope, down with dope, 1990; SR-27132; One Cause One Effect (Box 57)
          Catalog # V-15606; A-side Matrix # V-1-15606-Z2
        - One On One - Body music, 1981; SR-27133; One On One (Box 57)
          Catalog # BN-5551; A-side Matrix # BN 5551
          Bonus Records
        - One Way - One Way featuring Al Hudson, 1979; SR-27134; One Way; Hudson, Al (Box 57)
          Catalog # MCA-3178; A-side Matrix # MCA 1995 W1
        - One Way - Cutie pie; Give me one more chance, 1976; SR-27135; One Way (Box 57)
          Catalog # L33-1764; A-side Matrix # MCA-3044-W1
        - One Way - Shine on me, 1983; SR-27136; One Way (Box 57)
          Catalog # MCA-5428; A-side Matrix # MCA-3485-W2
        - One Way - Wrap your body, 1985; SR-27137; One Way (Box 57)
          Catalog # MCA-5552; A-side Matrix # MCA-4296-FDS4
        - One Way - One Way IX, 1986; SR-27138; One Way (Box 57)
          Catalog # MCA-5823; A-side Matrix # MCA-5934 FDS-5
        - O'Neal, Alexander - All true man, 1991; SR-27139; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 57)
          Catalog # Z 45349; A-side Matrix # PAL-45349-1A
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Hearsay, 1987; SR-27140; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 57)
          Catalog # 450936 1; A-side Matrix # 450936-1 A2
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Alexander O'Neal, 1985; SR-27141; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 57)
          Catalog # FZ 39331; A-side Matrix # PAL-39331-1A
        - O'Neal, Alexander - Hearsay - All mixed up, 1988; SR-27142; O'Neal, Alexander (Box 57)
          Catalog # MIXUP 1; A-side Matrix # MIXUP 1 A1
        - Ono, Yoko - It's alright (I see rainbows), 1982; SR-27143; Ono, Yoko (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27144. Different discs.
          Catalog # PD-1-6364; A-side Matrix # PD1634ASRE-1RM
        - Ono, Yoko - It's alright (I see rainbows), 1982; SR-27144; Ono, Yoko (Box 57)
          In same jacket as # SR-27143. Different discs.
          Catalog # 2391 559; A-side Matrix # 160 2391559 1 380
        - Opa - Magic time, 1977; SR-27145; Opa (Box 57)
          Catalog # M-9087; A-side Matrix # M-9078-A-1A
          Milestone
        - Opus - Up and down, 1984; SR-27146; Opus (Box 57)
          Catalog # 422-827 952-1 Y-1; A-side Matrix # 422827-952-1-AS-ES
        - Opus Seven - Thoughts, 1979; SR-27147; Opus Seven (Box 57)
          Catalog # SOR-72000; A-side Matrix # MCA 1981
          Source Records
        - Orange Juice - Rip it up, 1982; SR-27148; Orange Juice (Box 57)
          Catalog # 2383 651; A-side Matrix # 180 2383651 1 380 POLYGRAM
        - Orchestral Manoeuvers in the Dark - Georgia, 1981; SR-27149; Orchestral Manoeuvers in the Dark (Box 57)
          Catalog # AS 1403; A-side Matrix # XSM170008-1B
        - Orchestral Manoeuvers in the Dark - Architecture & morality, 1981; SR-27150; Orchestral Manoeuvers in the Dark (Box 57)
          Catalog # ARE 37721; A-side Matrix # P AL 37721-1A
        - Orient Express - Shine on me, 1982; SR-27151; Orient Express (Box 57)
          Catalog # DMD 355; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-43232-2
        - Originals - Naturally together, 1970; SR-27152; Originals (Box 57)
          Catalog # SS 729; A-side Matrix # SS 729
          Soul
        - Originals - Yesterday and today, 1981; SR-27153; Originals (Box 57)
          Catalog # JW 37075; A-side Matrix # JW-37075-AS-X
          Phase II Records Ltd
          Newnan, Georgia
        - Originals - Another time, another place, 1978; SR-27154; Originals (Box 57)
          Catalog # F-9546; A-side Matrix # F-9546-A-RE-2
        - Originals - Portrait of the Originals, 1970; SR-27155; Originals (Box 57)
          Catalog # SS 724; A-side Matrix # HS-1702-2
        - Originals - Down to love town, 1977; SR-27156; Originals (Box 57)
          Catalog # S6-749S1; A-side Matrix # S6-74951-2677-S-O6A
        - Orlando Riva Sound - Body to body boogie, 1978; SR-27157; Orlando Riva Sound (Box 57)
          Catalog # SA 8522; A-side Matrix # SA-8522-A
        - Orlando Riva Sound - Body to body boogie; Moon-boots, 1978; SR-27158; Orlando Riva Sound (Box 57)
          Catalog # SG 303; A-side Matrix # SG-303-A
        - Ortiz, Luis "Perico" - My own image, 1978; SR-27159; Ortiz, Luis "Perico" (Box 57)
          Catalog # T439; A-side Matrix # T-439-A
          Turnstyle Records
          Palisades Park, New Jersey
        - Osbourne, Ozzy - Diary of a madman, 1981; SR-27160; Osbourne, Ozzy (Box 57)
          Catalog # FZ 37492; A-side Matrix # P AL 37492-1B
          Jet Records
        - Osibisa - Mystic energy, 1980; SR-27161; Osibisa (Box 57)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # CAB LP 1002; A-side Matrix # CABLP-1002-A3
          Calibre
        - Osibisa - Mystic energy, 1980; SR-27162; Osibisa (Box 57)
          Catalog # 574008; A-side Matrix # 574008A
          Pye Records
        - Osibisa - Osibirock, 1974; SR-27163; Osibisa (Box 57)
          Catalog # BS 2802; A-side Matrix # T1 BS 2802-IF 40833
          Warner Bros. Records
        - Osiris - Since before our time, 1979; SR-27164; Osiris (Box 58)
          Catalog # TD-0001; A-side Matrix # TD-0001A
          Tom Dog Records
        - Osiris - O-zone, 1979; SR-27165; Osiris (Box 58)
          Catalog # 2234; A-side Matrix # MAR-2234-A-AM
          Marlin
        - Osiris - Since before our time, 1978; SR-27166; Osiris (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27167. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BSK 3311; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3311
        - Osiris - Since before our time, 1978; SR-27167; Osiris (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27166. 2 copies.
        - Oskar, Lee - Before the rain, 1978; SR-27168; Oskar, Lee (Box 58)
          Catalog # 6E-150; A-side Matrix # 6E-150-A RE-SP
        - Osmonds - Phase III, 1971; SR-27169; Osmonds (Box 58)
          Catalog # 1 SE 4796; A-side Matrix # 1SE4796 MGS2688
          MGM Records
        - Osunlade - Beats de los muertos (volume 1), 2000; SR-27170; Osunlade (Box 58)
          Catalog # YOR-015; A-side Matrix # YOR-015A
          Yoruba Records
          Greece
        - Otierre - Dalla sede (disc one), 1997; SR-27171; Otierre; Pina (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27172; SR-27173. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 436-1; A-side Matrix # 537905 1 1 520
          Italy
        - Otierre - Dalla sede (disc two), 1997; SR-27172; Otierre; Pina (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27171; SR-27173. Double album.
          Catalog # 537 436-1; A-side Matrix # 537906 1 1 520
        - Otierre - Dalla sede (disc two), 1997; SR-27173; Otierre; Pina (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27171; SR-27172. 2 copies.
        - Our Daughters Wedding - Lawnchairs; Airline, 1980; SR-27174; Our Daughters Wedding (Box 58)
          Catalog # 12EA 124; A-side Matrix # 12 EA 124 A-1
        - Our Daughters Wedding - Moving windows, 1982; SR-27175; Our Daughters Wedding (Box 58)
          Catalog # ST-17075; A-side Matrix # ST47075-26
        - OutKast - The way you move; Hey ya!, 2003; SR-27176; OutKast (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27177. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 82876-55883-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-55883-1-SA2 RE
        - OutKast - The way you move; Hey ya!, 2003; SR-27177; OutKast (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27176. 2 copies.
        - Outloud - Out loud, 1987; SR-27178; Outloud (Box 58)
          Catalog # 1-25632; A-side Matrix # 1-25632-A-SR1
        - Ovalle, Luis - El sonido de quisquella, 1976; SR-27179; Ovalle, Luis (Box 58)
          Different cover
          Catalog # LP-4367; A-side Matrix # DISCOLOR-4367-A
          Discolor Records
        - Fever Tree - Another time, another place, 1968; SR-27180; Fever Tree (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27181. Different discs.
          Catalog # US 1078; A-side Matrix # US-1078 TP
        - Overland Stage - Overland Stage, 1972; SR-27181; Overland Stage (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27180. Different discs.
          Catalog # KE 31319; A-side Matrix # PAL 31319-1A
        - Ozone - Li'l Suzy, 1982; SR-27182; Ozone (Box 58)
          Catalog # 6011ML; A-side Matrix # 6011ML-A-15A
        - Ozone - Gigolette, 1981; SR-27183; Ozone (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27184. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR-85; A-side Matrix # PR-85A-66336-D
        - Ozone - Gigolette, 1981; SR-27184; Ozone (Box 58)
          In same jacket as # SR-27183. 2 copies.
        - Ozone - Walk on, 1980; SR-27185; Ozone (Box 58)
          Catalog # M7-938R1; A-side Matrix # M7-938-R1-A-13B